Guide to the Kiwanis Club of Houston records, 1919-2017 MS 619
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XV: Photographs, 183248
  - 11 photographs, 8/1994-9/1994; 183307 (Box 58, Folder 59)
  - 4 photographs, 10/1994; 183308 (Box 58, Folder 60)
  - 23 photographs, 10/1994-11/1994; 183309 (Box 58, Folder 61)
  - 25 photographs, 12/1994-3/1995; 183310 (Box 58, Folder 62)
  - 4 photographs, 1/1995; 183311 (Box 58, Folder 63)
  - 14 photographs, 9/1995-10/1995; 183312 (Box 58, Folder 64)
  - 13 photographs, 10/1995-12/1995; 183313 (Box 58, Folder 65)
  - 25 photographs, 01/1996-03/1996 (Box 58, Folder 66)
  - 25 photographs, 4/1996; 183314 (Box 58, Folder 67)
  - 21 photographs, 7/1996-10/1996; 183315 (Box 58, Folder 68)
  - 20 photographs, 10/1996-2/1997; 183316 (Box 58, Folder 69)
  - 23 photographs, 11/1998; 183317 (Box 58, Folder 70)
  - 23 photographs, 9/1998-12/1998; 183318 (Box 58, Folder 71)
  - 24 photographs, 12/1998-4/1999; 183319 (Box 58, Folder 72)
  - 25 photographs, 4/1999-5/1999; 183320 (Box 58, Folder 73)
  - 24 photographs, 183321 (Box 58, Folder 74)
  - 36 photographs, 183322 (Box 58, Folder 75)
  - 14 photographs, 183323 (Box 58, Folder 76)
  - 8 photographs, 183324 (Box 58, Folder 77)
  - 9 photographs, 183325 (Box 58, Folder 78)
  - 13 polaroids, 183326 (Box 58, Folder 79)
  - Kiwanis Boys Work Committee photo, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 80)
  - Will C. Miller, Imperial Sovereign Mounted Photograph, 183328 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Mounted Black and White Photograph, 14 X 11, Three Men Receiving an Award, 183329 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - 12 Mounted Black and White Photographs, 8 X 10, 183330 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Mounted Black and White Photograph, 10 1/2 X 12 3/8, 5 Men with Charter, 183331 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Mounted Black and White Photograph, 9 3/8 X 7 3/8, 4 Men In Front of Trailer, 183332 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Mounted Black and White Photograph, 5 X 7.5, "Drug Abuse Has a Catch", 183333 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - William States Jacobs, Black and White Photograph, 183327 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Mounted Board Member Photographs (1 – 6), 183334 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Mounted Board Member Photographs (7 – 13), 183335 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Mounted Board Member Photographs (14 – 21), 183336 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Mounted Board Member Photographs (22 – 29), 183337 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Mounted Board Member Photographs (30 – 37), 183338 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Kiwanis Club Board Members, 183339 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - 13 Black and White Photographs; Note re: Kiwanis Club and Houston Lighting and Power Co. Luncheon; Drawing, 183340 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Color Slides- International Convention Houston, Colorado, 1966; 183341 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Color Slides- Golf, Tennis, End of Day Ranch, c. 1980; 183342 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Color Slides- Kiwanis Picnic, 5/30/1981; 183343 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Color Slides- Agr. Tree Planting, 183353 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Color Slides- "Kiwanis in Brief" Presentation, 183354 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Color Slides- Candid Shots/ People, 183355 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Color Slides- Golf and Tennis Shots, 183356 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Color Slides-International Convention Houston, Unlabeled Slides, 183357 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Color Slides- Unlabeled Slides (1 of 2), 183358 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Color Slides- Unlabeled Slides (2 of 2), 183359 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Color Slides- Assorted Slides, 183360 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Series XVI: Audio Cassettes, 183371
  - Club Board Meetings, 9 Cassette Tapes, 1986-1988; 183372 (Box 62)
  - Foundation Board Meetings, 10 Cassette Tapes, 1986-1987; 183373 (Box 62)
  - Speakers and Events, 36 Cassette Tapes, 1980s; 183374 (Box 62)
- Series XVII: Video and DVD, 183361
  - American Freedom Train- 1 VHS Tape, 1976; 183362 (Box 63)
  - American Freedom Train- 7 DVDs, 1976; 183363 (Box 63)
  - Kiwanis Roast for Fielding L. Cocke, Jr. VHS Tape, 1994; 183364 (Box 63)
  - Kiwanis Roast for Carlos R. Hamilton, Jr. VHS Tape, 1995; 183365 (Box 63)
  - Kiwanis Roast for Jack McGinty, Jr. VHS Tape, 2000; 183366 (Box 63)
  - Legends of Texas by Karen Stockton- VHS Tape, 183367 (Box 63)
  - Kiwanis Food Festival- VHS Tape, 1991; 183368 (Box 63)
  - Camp Periwinkle- VHS Tape, 1998; 183369 (Box 63)
  - Changing the World Forever, The Kiwanis Fight Against IDD- VHS Tape, 1997; 183370 (Box 63)
- Series XVIII: Awards
  - Kiwanis Bowling League Winners Trophy, 1944-1945 (Box 64, Item 1)
  - Christian Community Service Center award to Kiwanis Club (glass trophy), 2002 (Box 65, Item 1)
- Series XIX: Kiwanis Club Administration
  - Meeting Minutes-Board, 2007-2008 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes-Board, 2009-2010 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes-Board, 2011-2012 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes-Board, 2013 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes-Board, 2014 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes-Board, 2015-2016 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Agenda, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Agenda, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Achievement Reports, 1986-1999 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Club Election Reports, 1953-2003 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Greater Houston Partnership Membership, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Series XX: Financial records
  - Bequest: Carroll, Ilma W., 2002 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Bequest: Oden Foundation, 2008-2016 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Fire Insurance, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Fire Insurance, 1990-1994 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Fire Insurance, 1995-1999 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Payroll vouchers, 1983-1994 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Alliance Capital (dividend), 2003 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Fidelity Bond, 1985-2012 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Kiwanis International Liability Insurance, 2007-2010 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Workmen's Compensation Insurance, 1994-2012 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Series XXI: Membership
  - Membership: A-Ber (Box 66, Envelope 22)
  - Membership: Beverage (Box 66, Envelope 23-24)
  - Membership: Bi-Bla (Box 66, Envelope 25)
  - Membership: Blo- Br (Box 66, Envelope 26)
  - Membership: C (Box 66, Envelope 27)
  - Membership: D-Davis, L. (Box 66, Envelope 28)
  - Membership: Davis,R.-Di (Box 66, Envelope 29)
  - Membership: Dwyer (Box 66, Envelope 30)
  - Membership: E-Gr (Box 66, Envelope 31)
  - Membership: Hall-Hil (Box 66, Envelope 32)
  - Membership: Hinds (Box 66, Envelope 33-34)
  - Membership: Halsey (Box 66, Envelope 35)
  - Membership: I-Lea (Box 67, Envelope 1)
  - Membership: Led-Lu (Box 67, Envelope 2)
  - Membership: M-R (Box 67, Envelope 3)
  - Membership: Sa-Sch (Box 67, Envelope 4)
  - Membership: Sh-Sw (Box 67, Envelope 5)
  - Membership: T-W (Box 67, Envelope 6)
- Series XXII: Events
  - Jingle Bell Express, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Golf Tournaments, 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Golf Tournaments, 2000-2004 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Series XXIII: Grants
  - Aldine Y.O.U.T.H., 2008-2014 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Alley Theatre, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - American Lung Assn., 1985 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - American Red Cross, Houston, 1984-1997 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Amigos de las Americas, 1969-2015 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Archway Academy, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Arrow Child and Family Ministries, 2015-2016 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - AVANCE, 2012-2013 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Avondale House, 1987-1991 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Bering Memorial Methodist Church, Mayor's Emergency Shelter Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Big Brothers Big Sisters, 1990, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Bo's Place, 2003-2015 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Boys & Girls Country, 1992-2016 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Boy Scouts of America, Sam Houston Council, 1973-2012 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Bridges to Life, 2011-2016 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Camp for All, 1995-2002 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Casa de Esperanza, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Cenikor/Odyssey House, 2002-2016 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Center for Hearing and Speech, 1995-2016 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Child Advocates, 2002-2016 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Child Builders, 2010-2013 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Children at Heart Foundation, 2010 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Children at Risk, 2007-2016 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Christian Community Service Center, 1983-2017 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - "Cops and Kids", 1981 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Cossaboom Family YMCA, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Covenant House Texas, 1988-2006 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Depression and Bipolar Support Alliance, 2007-2013 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Dionysius Theatre, 2003-2004 (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Ensemble Theatre, 2003-2011 (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - ESCAPE Family Resource Center, 1995-2015 (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - Free Enterprise Institute, 1980-1996 (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - The Gideons International, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Gilbert & Sullivan Opera Society, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Girl Scouts, San Jacinto Council, 1989-2013 (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - Goodwill Industries, 1986-1994 (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - Gulf Coast Regional Blood Center, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Harris Foundation, 2011-2012 (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Healthy Family Initiatives, 2005-2010 (Box 67, Folder 48)
  - High School for the Performing and Visual Arts, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 49)
  - Houston Achievement Place, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 50)
  - Houston Area Women's Center, 2000-2013 (Box 67, Folder 51)
  - Houston Can! Academy, 2003-2005 (Box 67, Folder 52)
  - Houston Child Guidance Center, 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 53)
  - Houston Community Voice Mail, 1999-2004 (Box 67, Folder 54)
  - Houston Ear Research Foundation, 1984-2017 (Box 67, Folder 55)
  - Houston Food Bank, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 56)
  - Houston Pi Beta Phi Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 67, Folder 57)
  - Houston Habitat for Humanity, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 58)
  - Houston Preparatory Academy, 1994-1999 (Box 67, Folder 59)
  - Houston Toy Museum, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 60)
  - I Have a Dream, 1999-2008 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Interfaith Ministries, 1983-2005 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Junior Achievement, 1989-2004 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Mental Health Association, 1988-1994 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Multicultural Education and Counseling through the Arts, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Music Performance Trust Funds, 1992-1993 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Nehemiah Center, 2011 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Neighborhood Center, 2010 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Neuhaus Education Center, 1990-2010 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - New School in the Heights, 2009-2012 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Periwinkle Foundation, 1984-2011 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Post Oak YMCA, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - reVision Houston, 2014 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - River Performing and Visual Arts Center, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - RideOn, Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Ronald McDonald House, 1981-1984 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Salesmanship Club Camp for Children, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Salvation Army, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - The Seniors Place, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - The Shoulder, 1992-1993 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - SIRE, 2008-2015 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Spencer Home for Boys, 1977-1987 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Stehlin Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Stockton, Karen B., 1980-2002 (Box 68, Folder 25-26)
  - Texas Chamber Orchestra, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Texas Children's Hospital, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Twinning Project, 1992-1993 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - University of Houston for Amanda Posterick, 2002-2005 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - University of Texas Cancer Center, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - University of Texas Pediatric Burn Research and Education Fund, 1989-1993 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Volunteer Center Houston, 1990-2001 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - Weather Research Center, 2011-2013 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - The Women's Home, 2001-2012 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - Yellowstone Academy, 2009-2012 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - Young Life Greater Houston, 2001-2013 (Box 68, Folder 37)
- Series XXIV: Kiwanis International
  - Dues, membership lists, 1963, 1973-1980 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - Dues, membership lists, 1981-1990 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - Dues, membership lists, 1991-1995 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - Dues, membership lists, 1996-1998 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - Dues, membership lists, 1999-2001 (Box 68, Folder 42)
  - Dues, membership lists, 2002-2003 (Box 68, Folder 43)
  - Dues, membership lists, 2004-2007 (Box 68, Folder 44)
  - Key Clubs International, 1977-2002 (Box 68, Folder 45)
- Series XXV: Memorabila
  - Memorial folders (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - St. Agnes Academy scrapbook (Key Club contest), 1994-1995 (Box 69, Item 2)
  - Hirsch Fellow Awards (Robert L. Rowan, Jr., Carloss Morris, Dean L. Callender, Peter E. Pratt), 1996 (Box 70, Box 1)
  - Songs of Kiwanis songbooks (2), 1951 (Box 70, Envelope 2)
  - Songs of Kiwanis songbooks (2), 1965 (Box 70, Envelope 3)